Hello friends, today we will see
ICC Lombard's Super Top in which you will
get such features which will not be seen in any other policy. There are
not so many good features which we will
discuss in brief today. First of all, I will
tell you about ICC. This
company was started in 2001 and this company has
achieved many milestones in so many years
and
in 2020 it has
also acquired Indian General Insurance Company. So
as you can see on the screen, the
promise of more, so this booster is such a
good plan that if you
take 5000000 then you get 50 lakhs with it.
It has many features, let
me tell you about it.
First of all, you can remove it for lifetime
and in this you can keep two adults and three children
in a single policy and
if you want to keep a child, then you can also give individual policy to children from 3 months
to 5 years of age
and the post
normal waiting period is 2 years, tax
benefit, cashless hospital, so there are
hospitals around 10000 and  There is no policy check-up.
If you buy it before the age of 46,
you
can have three deductible options: ₹3 lakh, ₹
400,000, and ₹5 lakh. So, according to that,
you
get a super-duper plan. You
can get a ₹15 lakh plan with a ₹3 deductible. You can get a ₹50 lakh plan with a ₹4 lakh
deductible and a ₹5 lakh deductible.
[Music]
You have the
daily gas benefit, which
you can avail of, ₹348 accidental tax. You
can also avail of temporary total disability tax, in which you get some benefits
if there is a situation in
which you are not going to work and are
not doing it. Along with
this, you
can add critical insurance to it. So, we
hope it is a
very good plan. If you compare it,
its premium is also low and
you will get more features. If you
want a comparison or
you want to do any service
in the insurance sector, you
can contact us. You
can do that too.
What are the features in it?  If you want to understand something then
you can contact me, thank you.